Resume

Linus Dagerfall Vinnå

Backvägen 9 137 57 TUNGELSTA 073-903 18 98 linus.dv@gmail.com

Summary

Experienced Android-developer who is now retraining me as a UX designer with skills in requirements management to develop myself in another area of IT that I am really passionate about. Right now I am doing my internship at Qliro.

Work experience	
2018-01 – 2024-01	Android-developer Mathem
2017-06 – 2017-07	Summer job as presale IP-Only
2016-07	Summer job as presale IP-Only
2015-06 – 2015-07	Summer job as presale IP-Only
<u>Internship</u>	
2023-10 – 2024-04	Internship as a UX-designer Qliro
2017-09 – 2018-01	Internship as an Android-developer Mathem
Education	
2022-2024	UX designer with requirements skills Chas Academy 300 YH-p
2016-2018	Mobile Application Development Nackademin
2013-2016	Technical program Nacka Gymnasium

Other merits	
2022-	On the board of the student union Chas Academy
2022-	Student representative Chas Academy
<u>Diploma</u>	
2018	Degree certificate Mobile Application Development Nackademin

Language skills_

Swedish - Native language

English - Very good in speaking and writing.

French - I can speak and write French to some extent.

Computer knowledge

References

Be provided on request.